I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
あそこ:there (place physically distant from both speaker and listener)/over there|genitals, ステージ:stage, セッション:session
（蘭(らん)）あそこのステージで お前は
ダイブリとセッションするんだ
That's the stage where you'll
do a session with Dying Breed.
信ずる[しんずる]:to believe/to believe in/to place trust in, なんて:how ..!/what ..!|what (questioning), なんて:such as/(things) like|exclamation
（栄二(えいじ)）信じられません
彼らとやれるなんて…
I can't believe...
that I can play with them.
We need a huge event
for Belle Ame's debut.
デビュー:debut, 大きな[おおきな]:big/large/great, イベント:event, 必要[ひつよう]:necessary/needed|necessity
（蘭）ベルアームのデビューには
大きなイベントが必要なんだぞ
感謝[かんしゃ]:thanks/gratitude
（栄二）本当に感謝してます
I'm really grateful to you.
ビジネス:business
（蘭）栄二 これはビジネスなんだ
Eiji, this is business.
さすが:as one would expect|still/all the same, さすが:dagger, 全米[ぜんべい]:all-America/pan-American/all of America, 万[ばん]:many/all, 万[まん, よろず]:10,000|myriad|everything|, 枚[まい]:counter for flat objects (e.g. sheets of paper), 枚[びら, ビラ]:bill/handbill/flier, 売る[うる]:to sell, バンド:band, マネージャー:manager (e.g. of a business, an idol, etc.)
さすがに全米で800万枚売る
バンドのマネージャーだ
That manager was just what I expected
of a manager of an 8 million-seller band.
Our talks went smoothly.
話[はなし]:talk/speech|discussions, 話[わ]:counter for stories, episodes of TV series, etc., スムーズ:smooth
（蘭）話はスムーズだったよ
"Live 12
'Secret Live"'
英語[えいご]:English (language), バンド:band, いける:to arrange (flowers)/to plant|living, いける:to be good (at)/to go well|to look (taste, etc.) good
（エディ：英語）〈その
バンドは いけているのかい？〉
Hey, is that band any good?
ケビン:cabin, 英語[えいご]:English (language), もちろん:of course/certainly/naturally
（ケビン：英語）
〈もちろんだよ エディ〉
Of course, Eddy.
These guys are the
next big thing in Japan.
日本[にほん, にっぽん]:Japan, レコード:record (e.g. LP), 会社[かいしゃ]:company/corporation|workplace, 新人[しんじん]:new face/newcomer|modern humans (from Cro-Magnon man onwards)
〈彼らは日本のレコード会社の
イチオシの新人なんだ〉
ケビン:cabin, 相変わらず[あいかわらず]:as ever/as usual/the same, 強引[ごういん]:overbearing/coercive/pushy
（エディ）〈ケビンは
相変わらず強引だな〉
Kevin, you're pushy.
マット:mat
〈どうするマット？〉
What do you think, Matt?
マット:mat, 英語[えいご]:English (language), 気に入る[きにいる]:to be pleased with/to suit
（マット：英語）
〈リハで気に入ったら—〉
If we like them at the rehearsal...
yeah, we could play with them.
一緒[いっしょ]:together|at the same time|same, かまう:to mind/to care about|to care for
〈一緒にやってもかまわない〉
カモーン:Come on!, ビジネス:business, 頼む[たのむ]:to request|to call|to entrust to|
〈カモーン
これはビジネスなんだ 頼むよ〉
Come on. This is business. For me!
Hm...What are they called?
バンド:band
（マット）
〈そのバンド何ていうんだ？〉
〈ベルアーム〉
Belle Ame...It means
"beautiful spirit" in French.
フランス語[フランスご]:French (language), 美しい[うつくしい]:beautiful/lovely, 魂[たましい, だましい]:soul/spirit, 魂[こん]:Yang energy/spirit, 意味[いみ]:meaning/significance
〈フランス語で
“美しい魂”っていう意味だとさ〉
撮る[とる]:to take (a photo)|to record (video, audio, etc.)/to make (a film), やめる:to stop (an activity)/to cease|to cancel, やめる:to resign/to retire/to quit
〈おいジム 撮るのはやめてくれ〉
Hey, Jim! Don't film me.
やめる:to stop (an activity)/to cease|to cancel, やめる:to resign/to retire/to quit
〈やめてくれよ〉
Bugger off. Hit the road!
Why? Why not? I should let
everyone know how smart you are.
英語[えいご]:English (language)
（ジム：英語）〈いいじゃないか〉
いかに:how/in what way|however much, 優秀[ゆうしゅう]:superiority/excellence, 皆[みんな, みな]:all/everyone|everything, 教える[おしえる]:to teach|to tell|to preach
〈君がいかに優秀か
皆に教えてやろうぜ！〉
-No. Eddy...Can you tell him not to?
-Come on, over here.
（ケビン）〈ノー エディ〉
〈ヤツに
何とか言ってくれないか？〉
-Jim, give me that...
-Come on.
Give me that camera. I'll kick your ass.
I told you not to film.
うつす:to change/to swap|to change the object of one's interest or focus, うつす:to transcribe/to duplicate|to describe
〈うつすなって言っただろ〉
えーっと:let me see/well/errr ...
（竜介(りゅうすけ)）えーっと—
Uh...Eddy's guests...six of us.
ゲスト:guest
エディのゲストで
BECK(ベック) ６人です
"Registration for Participants"
Uh...Eddy's guests...six of us.
All right. Please sign here.
願う[ねがう]:to desire|to beg|to have something done for oneself
（スタッフ）はい それじゃ ここに
名前をお願いします
（千葉(ちば)）おっしゃー！
Awright!
（サク）竜介君…
Ryusuke-kun...
（千葉）おい コユキ！
Hey, Koyuki!
飛びつく[とびつく]:to jump at/to be attracted by
（千葉）さあ 飛びつけ！
Come on. Come at me.
千葉[ちば]:Chiba (city)
（コユキ）千葉くーん
Chiba-kun!
-Oh!
-Taa!
（コユキ）あー いってー…
Ouch!
見える[みえる]:to be seen|to look|to come, 見える[まみえる]:to have an audience|to face (an enemy)|to serve (esp. as one's wife)
（コユキ）見えないよ…
-I can't see...
-Koyuki!
もっと:(some) more/even more/longer
（真帆(まほ)）コユキー！
もっと前に行くぞ！
I'm going further up front!
男性[だんせい]:man/male|masculine gender, 客[きゃく, かく]:guest/visitor|customer, 客[まろうど, まろうと]:visitor from afar/guest, 歯[は]:tooth, 歯[よわい]:(one's) age, 弾く[はじく]:to flip|to repel|to use (an abacus)|, 弾く[ひく]:to play (piano, guitar)
（男性客１）おお 歯で弾いてる
-Oh...He's playing with his teeth.
-They're starting with
an imitation of Jimi Hendrix?
男性[だんせい]:man/male|masculine gender, 客[きゃく, かく]:guest/visitor|customer, 客[まろうど, まろうと]:visitor from afar/guest, いきなり:abruptly/suddenly/all of a sudden, 真似[まね, マネ]:imitating/copying|behavior
（男性客２）
いきなりジミヘンの真似かよ
Another minute, feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
No guarantees, but I'm so sure
She's into silence, candy for the head
Had a waking vision
I been so high ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly,
you gotta let go
Simply the most big sensation
once you're here you won't go back
She's really pretty, one-eyed vision
lose the fear it don't come back
Little sister showed me,
really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
Yeah, when I found you
My world came crashin' down
once you're here you won't go back
lose the fear it don't come back
コユキ あの人知ってる？
Koyuki, do you know who that is?
ミュージシャン:musician
（コユキ）え…
ミュージシャンなの？
Hmm...Is he a musician?
映画[えいが]:movie/film, 監督[かんとく]:supervision/control|director, 歳[さい]:-years-old|ability/gift, 歳[とし]:year|age|past one's prime
（真帆）映画監督の
ジム・ウォルシュ 28歳
He's the movie director Jim Walsh-
28 years old.
He's a brilliant filmmaker from New York.
ニューヨーク:New York (US state, city), 現れる[あらわれる]:to appear/to come in sight|to be expressed (e.g. emotions), 映像[えいぞう]:reflection|video|image in one's mind, 天才[てんさい]:genius/prodigy/natural gift
ニューヨークから現れた映像の天才
（コユキ）何でその人が？
Why's he here?
ツアー:tour, ムービー:movie, 撮る[とる]:to take (a photo)|to record (video, audio, etc.)/to make (a film)
（真帆）ダイブリのツアームービー
撮ってるんだ
He's shooting Dying Breed's tour.
飛び入り[とびいり]:open to all/taking part on the spur of the moment, ゲスト:guest, 紹介[しょうかい]:introduction/presentation/referral
〈ここで飛び入りの
ゲストを紹介します〉
I'd like to introduce our
special guest who just came in.
ミスター:mister/Mr
〈ミスター エイジ・キムラ〉
Mr. Eiji Kimura.
フン
（ケビン）フン
（蘭）フッ フフフ…
ついに:finally/at last|in the end
（栄二）ついに来たぜ
I'm finally here...
（マット）ヘーイ！
Hey! You really sucked at the rehearsal.
（栄二）俺のストラトが…
My Strat!
Your music won't save anybody.
音楽[おんがく]:music/musical movement, 結局[けっきょく]:after all|conclusion|ending of a game of Go, 救う[すくう]:to rescue from/to help out of/to save
〈お前の音楽じゃ 結局
誰１人救えないぜ〉
消える[きえる]:to go out/to vanish/to disappear
〈消えな！〉
Fuck off!
Hey, hey...They don't understand
the situation right here.
おいおい:Hey!/Wait a minute!|boohoo, おいおい:gradually/by degrees/little by little, 観客[かんきゃく]:audience/spectator/spectators, 状況[じょうきょう]:state of affairs (around you)/situation/circumstances, 理解[りかい]:understanding/comprehension/appreciation
〈おいおい 観客は状況を
理解してねえぞ〉
英語[えいご]:English (language)
（竜介：英語）
〈どうすんだ エディ〉
What'cha gonna do now, Eddy?
カモーン:Come on!
ええ？
（マット）カモーン
-Huh?!
-Come on!
マット:mat, 呼ぶ[よぶ]:to call out (to)|to summon (a doctor, etc.)|to invite||
（真帆）マットはコユキを
呼んでるんだよ
Matt's calling you, Koyuki.
歌う[うたう]:to sing|to sing (one's praises in a poem, etc.)/to compose a poem
〈さぁ 俺たちと歌ってくれよ〉
All right. You gotta sing with us.
男性[だんせい]:man/male|masculine gender, 客[きゃく, かく]:guest/visitor|customer, 客[まろうど, まろうと]:visitor from afar/guest
（男性客１）おい見ろよ
Hey, look!
男性[だんせい]:man/male|masculine gender, 客[きゃく, かく]:guest/visitor|customer, 客[まろうど, まろうと]:visitor from afar/guest
（男性客２）誰だあ？
-Who's that?
-He's Japanese.
日本人[にほんじん, にっぽんじん]:Japanese person/Japanese people
（女性客）日本人よ
男性[だんせい]:man/male|masculine gender, 客[きゃく, かく]:guest/visitor|customer, 客[まろうど, まろうと]:visitor from afar/guest, 子ども[こども]:child/children
（男性客３）まだ子どもだぜ
He's still a kid!
Hey, what'cha gonna play, dude?
（エディ）〈コユキ〉
Koyuki, what's your
favorite song of Dying Breed?
曲[きょく]:song/tune/composition, 曲[くま]:corner/nook|a shadow, 好き[すき]:liking/fondness/love, 好き[ずき]:-phil/-phile|being attractive (to), 歌[うた]:song|classical Japanese poetry (esp. tanka)|modern poetry
〈俺たちの曲で
好きな歌は何だい？〉
好き[すき]:liking/fondness/love, 好き[ずき]:-phil/-phile|being attractive (to), 曲[きょく]:song/tune/composition, 曲[くま]:corner/nook|a shadow
（コユキ）ええ…？
（真帆）好きな曲は何かって！
He's asking what your favorite song is!
ムーン:moon, ウォーター:water
ムーン・オン・ザ・ウォーター
Moon on the Water...
because I have special memory...
スペシャル:special, メモリー:memory
ビコーズ
アイ ハブ スペシャル メモリー
Full moon sways
Gentl...
こりゃ:hey there/I say/see here, マット:mat, ふざけ:play/sport/romp
〈なんだ？ こりゃ
マットのおふざけかい？〉
What was that?
A Matt's joke or something?
Full moon sways
Gently in the night of one fine day
On my way
Looking for a moment with my dear
Full moon waves
Slowly on the surface of the lake
You were there
Smiling in my arms for all those years
What a fool
I don't know 'bout tomorrow
What it's like to be
I was fool
Couldn't let myself to go
Even though I feel
The end
Old love affair
Floating like a bird resting her wings
Well, I don't blame him.
仕方ない[しかたない]:it can't be helped/it's inevitable/it's no use
（ミッちゃん）
まあ 仕方ねえけどな
He got up on the stage
with Dying Breed, after all.
たって:strongly hoping or requesting (of something that is difficult to be brought to fruition), たって:even if/even though|however, ステージ:stage, 立つ[たつ]:to stand|to find oneself (e.g. in a difficult position)|to depart (on a plane, train, etc.)
なんてったって ダイブリと
ステージに立ったんだもんな
But it's been a week.
週間[しゅうかん]:weeks (period of)
（千葉）でも もう１週間だぜ
A guitar expresses personality
through its six strings.
ギター:guitar, たった:only/merely/but, 本[もと]:origin|base|cause||, 本[ほん]:book|this|main||, 弦[つる]:bowstring|string (of shamisen, guitar, violin, etc.)|bail (arched pot handle)|, 弦[げん]:bowstring|string (of a shamisen, etc.)|chord|, 伝わる[つたわる]:to be handed down/to be introduced/to be transmitted, 出てくる[でてくる]:to come out/to appear/to turn up, 人間性[にんげんせい]:humanity/human nature
ギターってのは たった６本の弦を
伝わって出てくる人間性なんだ
英語[えいご]:English (language)
ねえ 竜介君 英語で言ってよ
Come on, Ryusuke...Say it in English.
Listen, Koyuki! You already had me
say it a hundred times. Quit it, will you?
（竜介）おい コユキ
回[かい]:counter for occurrences|a time|inning (baseball)||, 言わす[いわす]:to be able to say/to get someone to say/to induce someone to say, 勘弁[かんべん]:pardon/forgiveness/forbearance
俺 もう100回は言わされてるぜ
勘弁してくれよ
"A guitar..."
ギター:guitar
ギターっていうのは…
He's weird...
気持ち[きもち]:feeling|preparedness|thanks|
気持ちワリィ
Hi!
（真帆）ハーイ！
-Ray, we're in trouble.
-Maho is.
英語[えいご]:English (language), やばい:dangerous/risky|awful, やばい:wild Japanese apricot, 真帆[まほ]:spread-out sail/full sail/(sailing) downwind
（ヨシト：英語）
〈レイ やばいよ 真帆のヤツさ〉
-What? What's wrong?
-Uh-uh.
〈どうしたんだよ？〉
Hey, Yoshito...You tell
everything to my bro, huh?
真帆[まほ]:spread-out sail/full sail/(sailing) downwind, 英語[えいご]:English (language)
（真帆：英語）〈おい ヨシト！〉
兄貴[あにき, アニキ]:elder brother|one's senior|older man, 言いつける[いいつける]:to tell (to do)|to tell on (someone)|to often say, 気[き]:spirit|nature|motivation||, 気[げ]:seeming/giving the appearance of/giving one the feeling of
〈お前なぁ 何でも兄貴に
言いつける気か？〉
Yoshito's dad appears
in nine dramas every week.
ゴールデン:golden, ドラマ:drama
ヨシトのオヤジさん
ゴールデンのドラマに出てるんだぜ
Yeah. I heard that from Maho.
真帆[まほ]:spread-out sail/full sail/(sailing) downwind
ああ… 真帆から聞いたよ
おい ヨシト
Hey, Yoshito! This guy sang at
Dying Breed's secret live performance.
シークレット:secret, ライブ:live (esp. concert, show, etc.)/live performance, 歌う[うたう]:to sing|to sing (one's praises in a poem, etc.)/to compose a poem
こいつ ダイブリの
シークレットライブで歌ったんだぜ
（ヨシト）ふ～ん
You know...My dad brought
an actress to my house last day...
女優[じょゆう]:actress, 連れる[つれる]:to lead/to take (a person)
〈この前さぁ オヤジのヤツ
女優連れてきてさ〉
-Who was it?
-Guess who...
友人[ゆうじん]:friend, 英語[えいご]:English (language)
（友人：英語）〈誰だよ それ？〉
どういう:somehow/how/in what way, 意味[いみ]:meaning/significance
（コユキ）あれは
どういう意味だったんだろう…
I wonder what that was all about...
（斎藤(さいとう)）何だって!?
What's that?!
You mean we can't enter
the singing contest this year?!
今年[ことし, こんねん]:this year, 歌謡[かよう]:song/ballad, コンテスト:contest
（斎藤）それじゃ 今年の
歌謡コンテストには—
参加[さんか]:participation
参加できないって言うのか？
What do you mean,
the Neighborhood Board Chair is mad?
町内会[ちょうないかい]:neighborhood association/neighbourhood association, 長[たけ, たき]:height|length (esp. of clothing)|all (one has)|, 長[ちょう]:head|merit|superiority|, 怒る[おこる, いかる]:to get angry|to tell someone off|to be angular, そいつ:he/she|that
町内会長が怒ってる？
誰だそいつはー！
We've been practicing like crazy every day.
Shut up, will you? You nitwit!
連日[れんじつ]:day after day/every day, 猛練習[もうれんしゅう]:hard training, いい加減にしろ[いいかげんにしろ]:that's enough!/cut it out!/get a life!
連日猛練習してんだぞ
いい加減にしろ このバカチンが！
What's this all about?
どういう:somehow/how/in what way
どういうことなんだよ！
なあ こらー！
アハハ:a-ha-ha (laughing loudly)
あ… アハハ…
Long time no see.
久しぶり[ひさしぶり]:a long time (since the last time)/it's been a while (since I last saw, mailed, etc., you)
（泉(いずみ)）久しぶりだね
久しぶり…
Nice to see you.
I was in the neighborhood,
so I decided to stop by.
近く[ちかく]:near|nearly (e.g. "it took nearly one year")|shortly, 寄る[よる]:to approach|to gather (in one place)|to stop by (while on one's way to another place)||
（泉）ちょっと近くに来たからさ
寄ってみたんだ
You've been well?
元気[げんき]:lively/full of spirit|healthy
（コユキ）元気？
Yeah...You look well too, Koyuki.
元気[げんき]:lively/full of spirit|healthy
コユキも元気そうじゃない
I heard from Kayo-chan.
You sang with Dying Breed?
（泉）カヨちゃんに聞いたよ
ライブ:live (esp. concert, show, etc.)/live performance, 歌う[うたう]:to sing|to sing (one's praises in a poem, etc.)/to compose a poem
ダイブリのライブで
歌ったんだってね
That's awesome!
すごい:terrible/dreadful|amazing (e.g. of strength), じゃん:isn't it
すごいじゃん
Yeah...Matt called me up.
マット:mat, 誘う[さそう, いざなう]:to invite/to ask|to tempt
（コユキ）うん
マットが誘ってくれたんだ
背伸び[せのび]:standing on tiptoe and stretching one's back to make oneself taller/stretching oneself|overreaching oneself
（泉）ねえ コユキ…
背伸びたんじゃない？
Say, Koyuki...Haven't you grown a little?
同じ[おなじ, おんなじ]:same/identical|(usu. part of a 'nara' conditional) anyway
（コユキ）あ 斎藤さんにも
同じこと言われた
Saito-san said the same thing to me.
大人[おとな, だいにん]:adult, 大人[たいじん]:man of substance or virtue|giant|adult, っぽい:-ish/-like|tossing something out
何か 大人っぽくなったね
You seem more grown up.
Hmm...Maybe it's because I'm being
forced to swim 3 kilometers every day.
強いて[しいて]:by force, 毎日[まいにち]:every day
ん～ 強いて言えば
毎日３キロは泳がされてますから
I see...I haven't swum
for a while. I wish I could.
そっか～
久しぶり[ひさしぶり]:a long time (since the last time)/it's been a while (since I last saw, mailed, etc., you), 泳ぐ[およぐ]:to swim
私も久しぶりに泳ぎたいな
But I haven't got a swimsuit.
水着[みずぎ]:bathing suit/swimsuit/swimmers
でも水着ないんだよね～
You don't swim?
泳ぐ[およぐ]:to swim
（コユキ）泳がないの？
Then tomorrow...
あした:morning, あした:tomorrow|near future
じゃ あした—
Shall we go to buy me a swimsuit?
水着[みずぎ]:bathing suit/swimsuit/swimmers, 買い[かい]:buying|buyer|purchase
水着買いに行こうか
"Summer Sale"
I wonder if it's a little too small.
小さい[ちいさい]:small/little/tiny
（泉）ちょっと小さいかな？
I wonder if it's a little too small.
Well, it had been quite a while...
ホント:truth/reality/actuality, 久しぶり[ひさしぶり]:a long time (since the last time)/it's been a while (since I last saw, mailed, etc., you)
（コユキ）だって ホント…
久しぶりだったから…
変[へん]:strange|unexpected|change||
あ ごめん 何か変なこと言って…
I'm sorry if I said
anything I shouldn't...
彼氏[かれし]:boyfriend, 別れる[わかれる]:to part (usu. of people)|to separate (of a couple)|to lose (e.g. one's mother)
彼氏と別れたんだ…
（コユキ）えっ…
-I broke up with my boyfriend...
-Huh?
No more gloomy subjects.
暗い[くらい]:dark|dark (in colour)|depressed||, 話題[わだい]:topic/subject, おしまい:the end/closing|That's it
（泉）暗い話題はおしまい！
ん んん… ハァ～
Say...Let's go swimming!
泳ぐ[およぐ]:to swim
ねえ 泳ぎ行こ！
The public pool's closed today.
きょう:imperial capital (esp. Kyoto)|final word of an iroha-uta, きょう:bad luck/bad fortune|evil, 市営[しえい]:municipal management, プール:(swimming) pool, 休み[やすみ]:rest|vacation|dormancy (of a silkworm prior to moulting)
きょうは市営プール 休みだよ
Oh, Yukio...A girl named Maho's
been calling for you.
真帆[まほ]:spread-out sail/full sail/(sailing) downwind, 何回[なんかい]:how many times?, 電話[でんわ]:telephone call/phone call|telephone (device)
（コユキの母）ああ 幸雄
真帆って子から何回も電話あったよ
What? If she calls again,
tell her I'll call her back later.
かかる:to span/to bridge/to cross, かかる:to take (a resource, e.g. time or money)|to hang
（コユキ）え？
またかかってきたら—
かける:to hang (e.g. picture)/to hoist (e.g. sail)|to sit, かける:to run (race, esp. horse)/to dash|to gallop (one's horse)
あとで こっちからかけるって
言っといて！
（コユキ）
ハァ… ハァ… ハァ…
If you don't come, I'll go alone.
（泉）コユキが来なくても
私は１人で行ってるね
It's been a year since then...
あれから１年か…
Izumi-chan!
泉[いずみ]:spring/fountain
泉ちゃん！
コユキ 来てくれたんだ
Oh, you're here, Koyuki!
"School Facility-No Trespassing"
-Hurray!
-If you talk too loudly, they'll catch us.
やったー！
声[こえ]:voice, 大きい[おおきい]:big/large/great, バレる:to leak out (a secret)/to be exposed (a lie, improper behaviour, etc.) (behavior)
（コユキ）ああ… 声大きいと
バレちゃうよ
"School Facility-No Trespassing"
あんまり:remainder/rest|not very (with negative sentence), 膝[ひざ, ヒザ]:knee|lap/knee and thigh (while sitting), 曲げる[まげる]:to bend|to lean|to bend (the truth)||, 勢い[いきおい]:force|influence|impetus|, なくなる:to die, なくなる:to be lost (e.g. luggage)/to be missing|to be used up
（泉）分かる？ あんまり
膝を曲げると勢いなくなっちゃうの
Do you understand? If you bend your knees
too much it'll slow you down.
Uh-huh...
Koyuki...
コユキは…
Do you like Maho-chan?
真帆[まほ]:spread-out sail/full sail/(sailing) downwind, 好き[すき]:liking/fondness/love, 好き[ずき]:-phil/-phile|being attractive (to)
真帆ちゃんのこと好き？
Huh?
I'm talking about the
singing contest last year.
去年[きょねん, こぞ]:last year, 歌謡[かよう]:song/ballad, コンテスト:contest
（泉）去年の
歌謡コンテストのこと
I heard about it from Saito-san
a long time ago.
ずっと:continuously in some state (for a long time, distance)/throughout|much (better, etc.)
（泉）ずっと前に
斎藤さんから聞いたんだ
I have a feeling she likes you.
好き[すき]:liking/fondness/love, 好き[ずき]:-phil/-phile|being attractive (to)
（泉）彼女はコユキのこと
好きなんじゃないかな
気持ち[きもち]:feeling|preparedness|thanks|, 気づく[きづく]:to notice/to recognize/to recognise, 遅い[おそい]:slow|late (e.g. "late at night")|too late|, みたい:-like/sort of/similar to
（泉）私は 自分の気持ちに
気づくのが遅かったみたい
I guess I realized how I felt too late.
I was fool
（真帆）♪「MOON ON THE WATER」
Couldn't let myself to go
Even though I feel
The end
Old love affair
Floating like a bird resting her wings
U-Uh...
"Fireworks"
"Fishing Hole"
よろしく:well/properly|best regards, 願う[ねがう]:to desire|to beg|to have something done for oneself
（千葉）ははーい それじゃ
よろしくお願いしまーす…
"Fishing Hole"
All right. Thank you very much!
（平(たいら)）で 何だって？
So, what did they want?
They want to hear Beck's demo tape.
デモテープ:demonstration tape, 聴く[きく]:to hear|to listen (e.g. to music)|to ask||
BECKのデモテープが
聴きたいんだってさ
Yahoo!
ハハハ:ha ha ha (laughter)
イヤッホ～イ！ ハハハ…
-Hey, watch out!
-Alright!
危ない[あぶない]:dangerous|in danger|uncertain||
（平）おい 危ねえだろ
ハハハ:ha ha ha (laughter)
（千葉）やったー
ハハハ… フフフ…
Anyway, thanks to Koyuki,
Beck's riding a big wave.
おかげ:grace (of God)/benevolence (of Buddha)|assistance
とにかくコユキのおかげで—
ハハハ:ha ha ha (laughter)
（千葉）やったー
ハハハ… フフフ…
波[なみ]:wave, 波[ぽ]:Poland
BECKにもデカい波が
やってきたんだよな
ハハハ:ha ha ha (laughter)
（千葉）やったー
ハハハ… フフフ…
Music fans around the world
received shocking news today.
世界中[せかいじゅう]:around the world/throughout the world, 音楽[おんがく]:music/musical movement, ファン:fan
（アナウンサー）世界中の
音楽ファンに—
"Charismatic Singer Commits Suicide"
Music fans around the world
received shocking news today.
衝撃[しょうげき]:shock/impact/crash, 走る[はしる]:to run|to travel (movement of vehicles)|to hurry to||
衝撃が走りました
"Charismatic Singer Commits Suicide"
-Last night in New York,
-What?
アメリカ:America, 人気[にんき]:popularity/public favor|condition (e.g. market), 人気[ひとけ]:sign of life/human presence|humanity, 女性[じょせい, にょしょう]:woman/female|feminine gender, 歌手[かしゅ]:singer
アメリカの
人気女性歌手—
-Last night in New York,
-What?
ワット:watt
ワット!?
エリカ:erica/heath
エリカ・
ブライジさんが—
現地[げんち]:actual place/local/on-site, 昨夜[ゆうべ, ゆう]:evening|last night, 未明[みめい]:early dawn/grey of morning/gray of morning
現地時間の昨夜未明—
Popular American singer Ms. Erica Blige
killed herself in her hotel room
宿泊[しゅくはく]:lodging, してい:servant/janitor/messenger, してい:older sister and younger brother, ニューヨーク:New York (US state, city), ホテル:hotel, 一室[いっしつ]:one room
宿泊していた
ニューヨークのホテルの一室で—
ピストル:pistol, 自殺[じさつ]:suicide, 遂げる[とげる]:to accomplish/to achieve|to arrive at (a certain outcome)
ピストル自殺を遂げました
with a pistol.
Ms. Erica, a charismatic singer
with many fans in Japan,
エリカ:erica/heath, 日本[にほん, にっぽん]:Japan, 多く[おおく]:many/much/largely, ファン:fan, 持つ[もつ]:to hold (in one's hand)|to possess|to maintain||, カリスマ[カリスマ]:charisma (i.e. attractiveness, charm)|charisma (i.e. divinely conferred power or talent)|charismatic person|, 的[てき]:-like/typical, 歌姫[うたひめ]:songstress/diva
エリカさんは 日本でも多くの
ファンを持つカリスマ的歌姫で—
had CD sales of over 20 million worldwide.
全[ぜん]:all/whole|pan-, 世界[せかい]:the world|sphere|renowned|, 万[ばん]:many/all, 万[まん, よろず]:10,000|myriad|everything|, 枚[まい]:counter for flat objects (e.g. sheets of paper), 枚[びら, ビラ]:bill/handbill/flier, 超える[こえる]:to cross over/to cross|to exceed, セールス:sales/selling, 誇る[ほこる]:to boast of/to be proud of
全世界で2,000万枚を超える
ＣＤのセールスを誇っています
According to a spokesman, her new album
was to be released in a few months...
関係者[かんけいしゃ]:authorized people/authorised people/person(s) concerned, 筋[すじ, スジ]:muscle|vein|fiber||, 筋[きん]:muscle, 話[はなし]:talk/speech|discussions, 話[わ]:counter for stories, episodes of TV series, etc.
関係者筋の話では—
数か月[すうかげつ]:several months, 後[あと]:behind|after|after one's death||, 後[のち]:later|future|after one's death|, ニュー:new, ニュー:nu, アルバム:album, 発売[はつばい]:sale/offering for sale/release (for sale), 全米[ぜんべい]:all-America/pan-American/all of America, ツアー:tour
数か月後にニューアルバムの発売と
全米ツアーが…
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
マンボウ:ocean sunfish (Mola mola)
（千葉）
マンボウってさ—
Sunfish are cute, aren't they?
かわいいよね
"Live 13 'Ciel Bleu"'
Sunfish are cute, aren't they?
I wonder if they're edible...
食う[くう]:to eat|to live|to bite||
あれって 食えんのか？